<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on A minimal Hugo website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on A minimal Hugo website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>IISAGE</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>NSF Project Summary Overview We have established a Biology Integration Institute to determine how genome architecture, organismal biology, and phenotypic plasticity contribute to sex-specific aging and its evolution. In many species across the animal kingdom, one sex ages faster or has a longer lifespan. This sex specific aging has significant implications for conservation, agriculture, and human health. However, no unified model exists that reveals how mechanistic and evolutionary processes cause the diverse patterns of sex-specific aging seen in nature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Team</title>
      <link>/team/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/</guid>
      <description>IISAGE is collaboration among 11 research laboratories Lead Investivator Nicole Riddle, University of Alabama at Birmingham Co-PIs: Anne Bronikowski, Michigan State University Peggy Biga, University of Alabama at Birmingham Jerry Wilkinson, University of Maryland Erica Larschan, Brown University Ritambhara Singh, Brown University Ashley Webb, Brown University Ellie Duan, Cornell University Rich Meisel, University of Houston Toby Gamble, Marquette University James Walters, University of Kansas Please feel free to contact any of us about further details and to get involved in IISAGE.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
